Your smile is so cute.
笑顔がめっちゃ可愛いね
Thank you very much.
どうもありがとう
You look fine.
元気そうで
How are you?
お元気ですか?
yes.
はい
Can I ask you a few questions?
ちょっと色々聞いてもいいですか?
Your nose looks nice.
鼻並びいいね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Why is your nose lined up like that?
なんでそんな鼻並びいいんですか?
I don't know.
分からないです
I don't think it's my fault.
自分では悪いつもりなんですけど
It's not bad at all.
全然悪くないよ
Like Hai-chan.
ハイちゃんみたいな
How old are you now?
今は何歳ですか?
I'm 10 years old.
10歳です
Misunderstanding?
誤解?
I'm 10 years old.
10歳です
I can't stop my eyes.
目が止まらない
amazing.
すごい
How old are you?
何年生?
I'm a high school student.
高校生です
Is school fun?
学校楽しいですか?
I'm a little busy.
少し忙しいです
busy?
忙しい?
It's an exam.
受験なのね
Are you a test taker?
受験生なの?
Are you studying highly?
絶賛勉強中?
that's right.
そうです
Because it's a shame.
残念なのなので
Sorry for coming at such a busy time.
そんな忙しい時に ごめんね
Not really.
そうでもない
I turned the camera around like this.
こんなカメラ回しちゃって
You want to study right away, right?
すぐ勉強したいでしょ
What are you good at?
何が得意なの?
I'm good at English.
英語が得意です
Is that so?
そうなの?
Remember English words.
英単語覚えて
Are you not good at it?
苦手なの?
I guess it's Japanese history.
日本史とかですかね
Are you going to teach me?
教わそうなの?
yes.
はい
There's a death school, and I'm working towards that.
死亡校があって それに向けて
This is summer vacation, right?
今夏休みでしょ?
that's right.
そうです
Do you go to cram school?
塾とか行ってるの?
I'm going to cram school.
塾行ってます
A request?
申しとか?
Let's write a statement.
申しとか書きましょう
Can I ask about the death school?
死亡校は聞いちゃっていいですか?
Oh, where is it?
あ、どこなんですか?
This is Aoyama.
青山です
It suits you.
似合うね
Are you serious?
マジですか?
I want you to do your best.
頑張ってほしい
I will do my best.
頑張ります
I'm sorry to say that I want you to do your best.
頑張ってほしいって言いながら すいません
I will do my best.
頑張ります
Just a little distraction.
ちょっと気晴らしにね
Isn't it important?
大事でしょ?
do not have.
ない
Are you no longer involved in club activities?
部活とかはもうやってないの?
I have retired from club activities.
部活は引退しました
Retired.
引退した
What were you doing?
何をやってた?
I was doing gymnastics.
身体操をしてました
Gymnastics?
身体操?
yes.
はい
amazing.
すごい
Is your body soft?
体柔らかいんすか?
I think the body is probably soft.
体多分柔らかいと思います
What can I do?
何かできるんですか?
I think it's better if you can.
できるほうがと思います
That's a bit nice.
ちょっとそれいいっすね
Isn't it okay?
いいんでしょ?
It hurts.
痛いっすね
A little body...
ちょっと身...
I want to see a soft body.
体柔らかいの見たいな
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいですよ
Shoulder, something...
肩、何か...
rotate?
回転?
yes.
はい
Does that mean you can do paka?
パカってできるってこと?
yes.
はい
This way, this way, this way.
こう、こう、こう
That way?
そうやって?
Here, here, here.
こう、こう、ほら
Look.
ほら
Isn't it amazing?
すごいでしょ?
It's so cool.
パッカリじゃん
It's so soft, isn't it?
こう 柔らかいでしょ?
It's really soft.
本当に柔らかいんだね
Amazing, amazing.
すごい、すごい
I'm soft, so I am.
柔らかいんですから、私って
Something like forward bending?
前屈とかも?
You can also do forward bends.
前屈とかもできますよ
Huh, that's awkward.
へぇ、気まずい
This is amazing.
これはすごいね
It's soft, isn't it?
柔らかいでしょ
Please stand up for a moment.
ちょっとじゃあ、立ってさ
That was, uh...
あれは、なんか、あの...
Something that raises your legs.
足上げるやつとか
I can't do that.
できないですよ、それは
You can do it, absolutely.
できるでしょ、絶対
You can definitely do it.
絶対できるでしょ
I want to take a look.
ちょっと見たい
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけね
It's soft, isn't it?
柔らかいでしょ
amazing.
すごい
Because it's soft.
柔らかいんだから
Soft.
柔らか
That's amazing.
すごいね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
It's soft.
柔らかいんですよ
Hey, the teacher is coming today, so...
ちょっと、 ちょっと今日先生来てるから、
Hey yoga master.
ちょっとヨガマスター
Yoga master?
ヨガマスター?
I'm calling you a yoga master.
ヨガマスター呼んでるんで
Let me tell you a little bit.
ちょっと教えてもらおう
I'll come.
来ます
yoga master.
ヨガマスター
Is it?
ですか?
It's scary, isn't it?
怖いですよね
Can you do it now?
もうできるか?
Wow, that's amazing!
えっ、すごい!
It's pretty amazing.
結構、マジですごい
I'm serious.
ガチなんですよ
Really.
ガチ
It's serious.
ガチンコです
It's awkward.
気まずいです
Awkward?
気まずい?
What should I do?
どうしたらいいの?
this.
これ
Can you do it now?
今のできる?
I can't.
できないですよ
As expected, I don't have that kind of strength.
さすがに、その腕力はないから、私は
That's because I don't have the strength.
腕力ないから、 そういう声の
As for strength.
腕力は
My shoulders are stiff.
肩を凝ってる
I studied too much.
勉強のしすぎたの
My shoulders are stiff.
肩を凝ってる
So, it's just right.
ので、ちょうどいい
amazing.
すごい
I was surprised at his ability to cut his legs.
足をピロ切る技には びっくりしました
It's soft, isn't it?
柔らかいですよね
It's soft.
柔らかいですね
This is the master, right?
これがマスターなんですよね
yes.
はい
Well then, something that will make your shoulders stiff.
じゃあ、何か、 肩凝りのいいもの、
Do you have anything?
何かありますか?
There is.
ありますよ
there is.
あります
Now, please stand.
じゃあ、立ってください
Have you heard of it?
聞 いたことあるでしょ?
I've never heard of it.
聞いたことないですよ
No, I've never heard of that.
いや、それは聞いたことないですよ
I've never heard of that.
それは聞いたことない
Well, let me tell you.
じゃあ、教えておきます
He's tall, that kind of thing.
背高いですね、そういうの
That's right.
そうなんです
I'm tall.
身長高いんです
No, it's fine.
いや、いいです
Sorry this is so small.
こっちがちっちゃくてすみません
No, that's outrageous.
いや、とんでもない
So, when you kiss me, I'll stretch my back.
じゃあ、キスするとき背伸びしますね
No, that's awkward.
いや、気まずいですよ、それは
Huh?
えっ?
It's awkward.
気まずいですよ
You like kissing, right?
キス好きでしょ?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
That's naughty.
やらしいですね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Do the pressure points feel from the bottom to the top?
ツボって、 下から上の感じ?
Yes, probably.
そう です、多分
It feels like you can see it from below.
下から 見えていっちゃう感じですよ
that's right.
そうです
You're cute.
あなた、かわいいね
It's getting caught in my pants,
パンツの、 巻き込んじゃってるよ、
here.
ここ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいわ
Did you put on your pants in a hurry?
パンツ、 急いで履いたんですか?
that's right.
そうです
Roll-up pants.
巻き込み型パンツ
amazing.
すごい
Good style.
スタイルいい
amazing.
すごい
What do you call this fluffy dress?
このふわふわの服の なんていうんですか?
I never thought there would be a body like this under a dress.
ワンピースの下に、こういうボディがあるとは思わなかったです
What do you think?
どう 思う?
Please take a look, and see.
体見してください、しかも
Huh?
えっ?
It's good that you're up.
上がってていいよ
You're cute.
君、かわいいね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
If I don't have that, I'm just going to touch his penis.
それがなくば、ちんちん触りに行ってる
Yeah.
うん
Chin-chin, are you interested?
ち んちん、興味あるの?
Are you that embarrassed?
そんな恥ずかしいの?
Yeah.
うん
You're standing right there.
ちくりに立ってますね
It suddenly became quiet.
急に静かになっちゃった
You don't hate me, right?
嫌いじゃないでしょ?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Looks like it's coming from the right.
右から来るみたい
Can I see your pussy?
プッシー見ていい?
Do you understand Pussy?
プッシー分かる?
What did you think of English?
英語どう思わんかったの?
Will you take the test?
テストに出る?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
This is where it hit, right?
こっち、当たってたところでしょ?
It's transparent all the way here.
こっちまで透けちゃってるね
Do you mean pussy?
プッシーって言うの?
It's lazy.
だらだらだね
It's very wet.
ものすごく濡れてる
Looks like it's going to go through my neck.
首通りそう
It's getting really big.
めちゃくちゃ大きくなってる
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's so big that it almost goes through my neck.
首通りそう大きくなってる
I said it twice.
2回言っちゃった
Look at it that way.
首通りそう見てみて
Can't you see?
見えない?
But if you don't look at it, it will stay open forever.
でも見てくれないとずっと開きっぱなしだよ
Then let's watch it together.
じゃあ一緒に見よう
You both like being toyed with, right?
両方いじられるの好きでしょ?
yes.
そう
Mango's butt is sticking out so much.
マンゴーの尻すっごいっぱい出てる
Now, I want YG to do it one more time.
今さ、YGちょっともう一回やってほしいんだけど
Just do it for 10 seconds, YG.
10秒だけやって、YG
Stand up.
立 って
Stand up, stand up.
立って、立って
Oh no, this is coming out.
あ、やばい、これ出る
a!
あ!
It's out.
出ちゃった